# Ahmad F. Ibrahim

Hi there, I'm Ahmad Faidzal Ibrahim from Tangerang, Banten. My passion is to create apps and websites. I have experience Software Developer for more than 1 year, I am focusing on mobile apps development. however, some of my favorite projects involve working in Flutter for Android and IOS.

Jl Gama 19 No 51 Cimone Permai, Tangerang 0812-9421-9315

ahmadfaizal.i.afi@gmail.com <u>akhmadfaizal.github.io/Portfolio/</u> @akhmadfaidzal

# SKILLS AND PROFICIENCIES

- Dart (Flutter), Java, PHP, JavaScript, jQuery, NodeJS, API, React, MongoDB, MySQL.
- Teamwork, multitasking, open minded, focus on task and attention to detail
- Software and apps development

# **LANGUAGES**

- Indonesia (Native)
- English (Second Language)

#### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

- SMKN 4 Kota Tangerang
- SMPN 17 Kota Tangerang
- MI Plus Asy-Syukriyyah

#### **CERTIFICATION**

#### Dicoding

- Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Flutter untuk Pemula
- Memulai Pemrograman Dengan Dart
- Belajar Fundamental Aplikasi Android
- Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Android untuk Pemula
- Belajar Membuat Game untuk Pemula
- Memulai Pemrograman Dengan Kotlin
- Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web

## **WORK HISTORY**

## **Fullstack Software Engineer**

PT Indonesia Kreasi Mandiri | Oct 2020 - Now

Create web and app from zero, analyze, design, development, testing, and deploy the software.

#### **Junior Software Engineer**

PT Integra Pratama (Staff) | Sep 2019 - Dec 2019

Develop and deploy computer applications, code, and test programming for software and mobile apps. Execute code builds to test and production environments, fix bugs in existing code.

# Intern

PT Telkom | Feb 2018 - Mar 2018

Apply feedback from customers to improve service, and telecommunication also documenting branding results.

#### **PROJECT**

## PT Indonesia Kreasi Mandiri | Oct 2020 - Now

Kemanaa.com, invites you to explore more places, foods & Indonesian souvenirs, everything based on local favourites. Language: HTML, CSS(Bootstrap), Javascript(jQuery), PHP, MySQL.

Kemanaa App, language using flutter, firebase and database using SQLite.